Felipe Munevar

Buenos Aires, Buenos Aires Province, Argentina



felipemunevarn@gmail.com



+5491162314397



linkedin.com/in/felipemunevarn

Summary

Fullstack Web Developer with knowledege in JavaScript, CSS, HTML, React / Redux, Node.js, PostgreSQL, SQLite, Sequelize, Testing (Mocha, Jasmine, Chai) and Git, Spanish native. Certifications in Python and MySQL. Large experience developing engineering projects with different teams. Great sense of responsability and results oriented skill. I am quiet excited about software developing and desiring to learn and to improve in it.

Experience



Senior Structural Engineer

SEIBO

Jun 2016 - Aug 2016 (3 months)



Junior Civil Engineer

ROMERO, RICARDO

Jan 2006 - Apr 2006 (4 months)

Research Intern

Manufacturas de Cemento S.A

Jul 2005 - Dec 2005 (6 months)

Education



Cisco Networking Academy

NDG Linux Unhatched, Computer Programming, Specific Applications Jan 2021 - Jan 2021

Linux knowledge



(A) freeCodeCamp

Fullstack web developer, Programación informática, general 2020 - 2021



UNAL Colombia

Civil Engineer 2000 - 2006

Skills

Engineering • Project Management • English • Communication • Analytical Skills • Slack